articlegeek.com 2013-05-24

# ArticleGeek Privacy Policy

Welcome to ArticleGeek.com (the "Site").

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by ArticleGeek.com (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").

**"Personally Identifiable Information"**   
refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name and email addresses. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user)   
or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**  
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following information from our Authorized Customers: the names, websites and email addresses of Authorized Customers (if given).

**What organizations are collecting the information?**  
At this time, ArticleGeek.com is the only party with access to user information. We do not control how third parties (advertisments on the site) use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We only use Personally Identifiable Information to email Visitors and Authorized Customers about the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. 

**With whom may the information may be shared?**  
We do not share any Personally Identifiable information with third parties. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by ArticleGeek.com is securely stored in log files and databases and is not accessible to third parties or employees of ArticleGeek.com except for use as indicated above. 

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at 

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used when visitors access the ArticleGeek.com author area. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Authorized Customers and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 20 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off. 

**How does ArticleGeek.com use login information?**  
ArticleGeek.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use within the ArticleGeek.com website, and gather broad demographic information in order to enhance the usability of the site.

**What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?**  
No outside partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information. Any changes to this third party policy would be posted in this privacy policy. 

**Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law.**  
We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers. 

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers is not and never will be collected. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences. 

**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at 

**Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?**  
We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting . However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward. 

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure. 

**External Links:**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We **strongly** encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours. 

* * *

©2006 [ArticleGeek.com: Free Website Content](http://www.articlegeek.com/) \- All Rights Reserved
